Hubungi

+6281774971925 (Work) fikri.raihan4@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/fikriraihan (LinkedIn)

fikri-portofolio.netlify.app/ (Portfolio) github.com/Fikriraihan (Portfolio)

Keahlian Teratas

Vite

Shadcn

Mantine

Certifications

Legacy JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures
Intro to Digital Marketing

Fikri Raihan

Frontend Developer

Area DKI Jakarta

Ringkasan

Hi! I'm Fikri Raihan, a frontend developer who enjoys building clean and user-friendly web applications. I specialize in delivering smooth user experiences using React.js and Next.js.

I'm passionate about turning ideas into real, interactive products and constantly exploring new tools to improve my skills. I love staying upto-date with the latest trends in frontend development.

Let's connect and share ideas!

Pengalaman

Planet Surf Frontend Developer Agustus 2024 - Present (11 bulan) Jakarta, Indonesia

PT Reycom Document Solusi Frontend Developer Februari 2023 - Agustus 2024 (1 tahun 7 bulan) Jakarta, Indonesia

Harisenin.com Frontend Developer September 2022 - Januari 2023 (5 bulan) Jakarta Metropolitan Area

FXMedia / FXMWeb Frontend Developer Mei 2022 - November 2022 (7 bulan)

harisenin.com Student of Full-Stack Web Developer Maret 2022 - Juli 2022 (5 bulan) Immersive training program with an emphasis on Full-Stack Web Development

Himpunan Mahasiswa Departemen Fisika Universitas Indonesia Vice Chairman of Entrepreneurship

Januari 2019 - November 2019 (11 bulan)

Depok, West Java, Indonesia

 Work directly with the Head of Entrepreneurship Division manage and command innovation to fund the income for HMD FISIKA UI

- Calculating income and expenses

Material Student Science Society Fisika UI Finance Staff

Januari 2019 - November 2019 (11 bulan)

Depok, West Java, Indonesia

Gave financial support to organization event with merchandise and fundraising

Dish.troyer Small Business Owner September 2018 - Februari 2019 (6 bulan) Jakarta Metropolitan Area

BEM FMIPA UI

Public Relations Staff

Januari 2018 - November 2018 (11 bulan)

Depok, West Java, Indonesia

- Social media posting through Instagram, Facebook, Twitter, and LINE platforms (5 posts per day on an average basis)
- Create and manage offline publication (wall magazine)
- Quality control of content and caption for social media posts
- Manage and conducting "Grand Launching" event

Pendidikan

Universitas Indonesia (UI)
Bachelor's degree, Physics · (2017 - 2021)

Zero To Mastery Academy
Data Structures and Algorithms